[Music]
so why we call the product qualia most
people won't know what that word means
and it'll just sound like a cool name
hopefully a cool name but for those who
do the term comes from philosophy of
mind and quality refers to the
subjective experiences that make up
someone's subjective landscape the
quality of what it is like to exist and
to being you so where the physical
universe is made up of particles and
physical force fields subjective
universe is made up of emotions and
feelings and impulses and intuitions and
meaning and these are known as quality
it's a subjective substrate spewing
experience of naming the product qualia
were alluding to the idea of condensing
not just some very limited aspects of
cognitive capability like short-term
memory and long-term memory but
enhancing the quality of what it was
like to be enhancing your experience of
navigating existing and that's lost in
its Baigent aspiration is really what
we're shooting
[Music]